[Applause]
[Music]
hey guys thank you for joining the
livestream as you can see from the title
this video is going to be about
embedding payloads in android apk this
is a video that has been requested
for quite some time and so i'm gonna be
showing you that in this particular
video so again the whole idea was to do
it manually so that's primarily what I'm
going to be doing so by default I
already have downloaded in an apk here
I'm going to be using the Bitcoin wallet
to be demonstrating this so I'll be
taking you through the overall process
of doing it so the first thing that
we're going to be doing is generating
the payload with MSF venom so no
obfuscation yet so after we regenerate
the payload we're then gonna within a
kinetic compile the payload with apktool
and then we'll also use our our
particular APK of choice and also
decompile it and i'll show you how to
embed the payload or inject the payload
into a particular application or APK
file alright so let us get started here
so the first thing of course we are
going to need to do is we are going to
need to generate our our payload with
MSF venom alright so let's do that right
now so I myself venom Peep and that
that's our payload and of course with
metadata there are various modules that
you can use so for example you can use
the reverse tcp reverse https etc so
river android the temperature and
reverse tcp I'll be stopping during the
video to answer your questions so yeah
you can just post them right over there
and I'll be answering them so
meterpreter reverse reverse TCP and then
of course you can set your L host to
192.168.1.1 o8 and your airport I'll set
that to just 1 2 3 4 and again you then
you then move on to search or to
actually outputting the file so we'll
just call this a payload dot apk and oh
my I'm on my desktop but anyway I'll
just copy that file there so I will
generate the payload and then we can
then also we'll start decompiling the
payload first I'll show you how to do
that with
pick a tool so that's the first thing
we'll be doing and then we can start we
can actually start decompiling
the the other Android application so
there are many applications that you can
use so yeah I'm gonna be answering the
questions as the video essentially takes
its time during the process apologies if
my machine is a bit slow here I'm using
a virtual machine with very stringent
resources so there we are the payload
has been generated and we can actually
get started now alright so I'm just
going to copy the payload from this
directory into our desktop here and we
move into our desktop now and we have
our apk right over here so - you are
actually decompile an application with
apktool we can I can click an apk tool
here and then of course we decompile
which is denoted by the D command and we
use the F command and then we specify
the application so payload apk that is
if it is in D working
if it is in the working directory so
otherwise you need to specify the
directory of the application so then we
then move on to the output where we want
to output the file so I'm just going to
say root desktop the decompiled
information and I'll just call it
payload into the payload folder and hit
enter and that is going to start ddeok
the decompiling the application alright
so we will then move on and let me turn
on some questions here so the syste
internals have a decompiler sysinternals
is more focused on windows and windows
management I'll be making a video on
that as well this payload only works on
your local network or you can set up
port forwarding that is if you have
static IP so that it does work unless if
you have a dynamic IP then if it's going
to keep on changing then you might not
have a persistent session so it's always
good to have a static IP for that
alright so the D compilation is
completed so I'm just gonna list the
files in here and you can see that we
have the payload folder right over here
now the interesting thing that you can
actually do with with
payload so if I switch into the payload
directory here we have the
androidmanifest.xml we have the apktool
dot yet at the ml file here which are
not working with we working with the
small e folder which is the assembler
which can be considered an assembler for
Android so if we go into the small e
folder this is where we will have our
comm Metasploit and the stage directory
all right so if I change into the comm
right away and we have the Metasploit
and then you'll find the payload file
within the Metasploit folder and within
the this stage so if I just hit enter
there we are so we have the payload the
payload small D file right over here so
general editing of the payload
application is very very simple so if I
was to just go back into my previous
directories here sorry about that let me
just take you a step back so we can
actually take a look at the Android
manifest so the Android manifest is
where you can essentially edit the
permissions for your payload but of
course we'll be looking at that in a
second so if I just browse onto my
desktop here let me just open that up
apologies this is taking a while desktop
and are we going to our payload here and
Android manifest dot XML and yeah there
we are so we have our permissions in
here and what we'll be looking for one
will be decompiling or other application
in which will be embedding the
particular payload is we're looking for
the main activity alright now this is
going to be very important but of course
this application has no other activity
so the default one will be the oncreate
for the main activity if you've ever
done Android programming all right so
we're looking particularly for these two
lines of code we're looking for the
Android intent action main that is the
most important one right over here and
from that you'll get the application
source so right over here is where you
can edit your your permissions but these
are going to be important especially
when embedding the Metasploit payload
into your into your other other Android
application so let's get let's actually
get started on that right now so what
I'm going to do is I'm just going to
take a step back here and I'll just copy
the application which is the Bitcoin
wallet I believe I'll sorry that is in
my downloads folder
my downloads folder like so and that is
in comm I believe what is the
application name not sure it's telling
me what my application name is did I
actually download the application let me
just check
I should have got it right over here
yeah there we are it is the the shell
bat or wallet so let me just copy it
here directly so we can actually speed
this up all right so we can get started
with the D compilation all right so in
here we can start D compiling this so
apktool again APK to be compiled F and
then we specify the application here
sorry this is on my Android yeah sorry
about that
the the application here we output this
I'll just call this desktop and we will
call this the original the original APK
and hit enter
all right let me take a look at the
questions here that we're getting Ryan
no that's that's not a question for me
how to get a static IP that will depend
on your ISP and how many and what IPS
they've given you max fire says noob
yeah if you say so
good hustle how's everyone doing alright
a DD compilation is complete we can
actually move on alright so now we need
to go into the original folder here and
this is what we'll be doing most of the
editing so again the first thing you
want to do is you want to actually
create the Metasploit stage folder
within the smally folders also you have
to do there under calm so smally we
enter here so don't go into the forum
directory we hit enter and in here we
need to create the Metasploit so we just
we just create the Metasploit stage
folder so m'kay there are Metasploit CD
Metasploit and make directory we'll just
call this stage and that will change our
directory into stage so now what we need
to do is we need to copy that initial
payload from the Metasploit stage folder
into the the small EECOM Metasploit
stage folder as well so that's the first
thing we need to transfer the payload
and then I'll show you how to actually
add that line of code after we do during
the main activity so what I'll be doing
for this video because I have a few
minutes left that I can actually live
stream I'll be actually recording
follow-up videos for this showing out to
sign the apks and now to obfuscate them
so let's do that first so what I'm going
to resolve is gonna say coffee root
desktop and we are looking for the
payload so payload what what are the
directories we have in here so failure
there we are
we have the smoly folder and we want to
go into comm Metasploit and we want the
payload the if we actually get the stage
and the payload that's Molly file right
over here and we will copy that again
from that directory
rude desktop and we are moving into the
original so original small e small e
comm Metasploit stage and enter and we
should have the file in there alright so
that is the payload right over here
before we actually move on exploit will
this video be accessible after the
stream yes it will be
that's primarily was making this video
because it was just Narayan mahoto asks
me what I'm doing and a very obscure way
but anyway I'll just I'll just forget
that ever happened so now that we have
the payload dot small e file within the
Metasploit stage folder created under
the array original APK file we can
actually get started with editing with
editing the the Android manifest file
however the first thing as I mentioned
we need to do is we need to look for the
the main activity that is going to be
launched when the application starts off
first so what happens is when we start
that the application first for the first
time as you do with Android for any of
you have done Android programming the
main activity is what is started so we
are primarily looking for that so we're
gonna go into original Android manifest
open with text editor and now this is
where the exciting stuff is so you can
go ahead and take a look at the minimum
SDK requirements and again what we're
looking for is the Android intent action
dot main and the activity will be just
listed as a as the top right over here
so this these two go under the the
activity alias which is listed as well
over here so we're looking for
de-shelled batch wallet UI wallet wallet
activity alright so we're gonna look for
that directory right now so that is de
and that is under small e again so small
e de
shell batch wallet and we're looking for
the UI so we're going to look for the UI
folder here and we're looking for the
wallet activity alright so we can hold
activity there we are and we can open
that up with TextEdit
and now we're looking for the oncreate
function all right so the uncrate again
is very important because we are looking
for the land raid OS bundle so we can
add the line right over here now many of
you will be wondering now we like will
actually and it will add it a be below
the invoke super so this is a we're
going to be invoking a static one and
that again is going to be launching the
payload on well during an on create
function which again is going to utilize
a deal android right over here
alright so now we can actually get
started here so the first thing as i
mentioned we're going to get started
with is we need to start copying those
particular files so before we actually
before you actually move ahead with this
video let me just explain what's going
on so we are going to be going into the
wallet activity which is going to be
launched during the b1 the application
is launched and so during that
application we're going to use the
oncreate as well here to essentially
load up the payload thoughts mali file
that we actually copied alright so let
us actually get started so what i'm
gonna do is let me just go through your
questions or i'll actually go through
them after this so the first thing we're
gonna do is we're going to go to a line
we will go right over here we need to
have it below the on cradle android that
users utilizes the OS bundle here so
we're gonna say sorry there we are there
there it is so I'm just gonna indent
appropriately so invoke static and again
we're going to use a p0 so p0 here in
curly braces so p0 and I'll explain what
all of this is I'm plan on making a
separate video for this because again I
am going to be stop confusing people if
I go on with that so invoke static and
then we're gonna use the alcohol which
is the the comm folder so al comm and
then the Metasploit folder Metasploit
and then you have your stage and the OPP
up you have your payload here which
again is in payload you don't need to
specify that it is a small e file so you
can leave the extension so then that is
going to bring us up into the oncreate
function so on on create and then now
we're utilizing land roid again so all
Android the content and in the context
so we'll it launch every time
the the wallet activity is started up
which is the main activity when the
application starts up so yeah there we
are so that'll essentially launch any
payload and if you have created the
payload appropriately you set up your
your exploit multi handler and you're
pretty good right over there to get
started so on create and then we're
using the we're using land right orell
Android whatever your Nepal it for those
of you content and then context context
and then we close that up and we use the
capital V and we can then save this file
alright now that we're done with that
you now need to start copying the
permissions you require and this is
unique for every application because as
you can see the Bitcoin wallet
application allows for these permissions
okay they allows the camera to be used
it allows a wakelock which is very very
good
a lot of Bluetooth NFC the network state
allows you to access the network state
so it has many of the important ones
that we have here so what we're going to
do is we are going to copy the important
ones and those are going to be are going
to do with the the course location the
file location the phone state send them
as SMS received as a mess record audio
call phone read contacts write contacts
record audio camera write external
storage we don't need the wallpaper
panel just get rid of it from there so
we'll copy these will copy the Android
permissions here and we will paste it in
and delete the duplicates from here so
again I will delete did the the
duplicates so let me just look for one
of them that I know we did have here
that was the wakelock
which I'm sure was up right over here
write call log set wallpaper we don't
need that one so let's get rid of that
first receive boot completed camera
settings right settings yeah that's fine
I believe I saw wake lock here but I
think yeah that should be it so yeah we
don't have any duplicates so that's
excellent so we're gonna save that
manifest file here and we are ready to
go we're ready to compile the
application so what we have done
essentially till
let me answer some questions before we
actually recompile so what we have done
till now is we have we have essentially
embedded the the MSF venom payload now
one thing to take into consideration is
we have not particularly obfuscated the
Android application which means there is
going to be some detection some level of
detection I'll probably be making
another video on this where I'll
actually show you how to perform the
obfuscation on a particular Android
application and your if you want to
perform obfuscation I believe I have one
of these links here that we used to use
before and that is apk wash apk wash
allows you to essentially obfuscate or
generate as you can see right over the
android apk antivirus evasion for MSF
venom generated payload so this allows
you to obfuscate various MSM MSF venom
payloads and of course I know that
embedding or injecting a payload with
MSF venom all already exists and yeah
someone is just pointed out that the
camera is a duplicate permission so let
me just check that out right now
looks like we have we also have read
context of those read and write contacts
let me check this right over here I can
see camera right here let's see if we
can find there we are thank you very
much for pointing that out
thanks for pointing that out really
appreciate that I was probably looking
for wakelock as well but it really
shouldn't cause an issue so let me just
save this right now and we can get
started with it with the recompilation
all right so we want to recompile the
original apk here and we can do that
right now so what we can do is we can
essentially recompile from any directory
so apk to and we'll say build and then
we can specify the directory again so
root desktop and then we specify the
original folder here now this is where
things get very very important when you
talk about using applications like the
or scripts like the fat rat for example
the fat rat is a tool that generates
most likely to - a - to great success a
signed payload apart from embedding
applications which we know is very very
difficult to do
matically because you usually get errors
so if you do get an error here if we do
get an error then I probably have to
take a deeper look at the application so
I'm just going to try and compile it
once to recompile it once if it doesn't
compile then I'll probably have to find
another application but I just wanted to
make a quick live stream for this video
so let me just answer a few questions
before we carry on use T mocks and I
wrote it under advice yes more hundred
videos are coming that's primarily why
I've started with this right now term ax
hacking excellent yes it is it's very
very good very good application yeah we
have a good question here telling us
I've tried the fat rat it failed with
signing yes that's probably because it
uses zipper line and I'm not sure if
we'll get an error right now we probably
will but let's see what error we get and
I'll probably try and and understand
what's going on now this is where real
skill comes into play because if you're
going to manually embed if you're going
to manually embed these these payloads
into applications it also gives you an
opportunity to test which applications
allow you to embed these various
payloads because some applications will
not recompile at all so it's very very
important to take that into
consideration so I've recently started
the recompilation process and this looks
like it's going to work and again it
tells us that it failed right over here
so let's take a look at what actually
caused the error and immediately we get
the a apt error which I'm not going to
explain what it is right now so if we
take so all right so if we take a look
at this right over here you can see that
by default
yes I'll be uploading the video after
you can see that we've got an error and
it's all is giving us an error in the
Android manifest file first but the main
issue is with the aapt which means we
probably need the Android SDK installed
because of the various requirements so
what we can do is we can just try and
download another application here
probably a simpler application let me
just find one that's very
again very very simple I'll just let me
see if I can find another application
what if the main activity is hidden
there must be a main activity that's a
very very good question
in fact I'll just answer question I'll
make a separate video on this even if
the main activities yeah that's a very
good question so every application will
be designed differently and usually what
again what you're looking for is the
Android dot intent not main if you can
find those two lines where it actually
specifies the intent dot main and it
also specifies the icon or the drawable
icon if it's right over there then you
essentially know that the one of the the
the the top group right over there that
contains the the activity is going to be
the main activity so your job is to look
for that within these small E is to look
with for that within the small e
compiler
alright so also the fat reduction yes
that's a very good question the fat rat
does not provide obfuscation it simply
signs the application so if I was to
compile this application I remember the
Google now launcher did work with the
recompilation so I'll do that for you
guys once more time or once again so
I'll download this here and I'll do it
again with you guys this this did work
what you will find is after I have
recompile the application I need to sign
it and that's where probably I can use
the fat rat or I'll actually be making a
separate video showing you how to do
this so I have downloaded the
application let me just wait for that to
complete let me see if that is a
downloading I probably yeah any well
I'll just wait for that to complete so
in the meantime what I'll do is I will
just go back to to my desktop here we'll
keep the payload I'll get rid of the the
Bitcoin wallet application here and I
will get rid of the original folder
which contained our our decompiled
application so we have the payload at
our APK here which we D compiled and if
we just list the files in here sorry for
that if we list the files we have the
payload folder which contains the
payload itself which is the most
important bit
we thought was once we start embedding
so again hopefully this just finishes
downloading for some reason it did not
start downloading apologies for that let
me just try and save my internet does
not seem to be working right now or has
it downloaded my browser is unresponsive
sadly so let me just read let me just
list let me just list my downloads
folder here looks like we do have the
the application has completed
downloading so if I can just check the
size of this looks like one of them is 8
megabytes yep so that looks like it's
completed so I'll just copy that um I'll
just copy the Downloads that let me just
get rid of that there and we'll just
copy the I will just copy the
application to the desktop and we can DD
compile that immediately alright so copy
the downloads and we'll copy the com
Android launcher desktop and on it enter
and for some reason looks like the files
[Applause]
looks like the Downloads did not
complete sorry root downloads keep keep
getting confused with that let me just
check the downloads it looks like they
haven't completed yet but for some
reason my my my browser isn't working
let's see if it does prompt us to
actually download that in any case I'll
just copy I'll just delete the the
duplicate one right over here and
hopefully we can actually copy them now
so I'll just copy this
alright enough to speed through this
process now so that I can actually show
you that the compilation does work so
what we'll do now is we will use the
apktool apktool decompile and we'll come
go go right over here and we'll call
this original hit enter for some reason
oh sorry I forgot the output file that
is the output parameter right over here
and we're just gonna wait for this to
decompile so let me just answer some of
the questions yes I have duplicates just
saw that download it the fault twice so
yeah we've decompiled the application
let me just try and answer one more
question let me just see if we have any
other questions before I continue
what is this for this video is focused
on how to manually embed payloads msfn
and payloads are in android apks at
least I got to see you brother
Salam hello Naheed thank you for joining
the stream yeah the slaw looks to be
like the only questions there all right
so we can get started now so I'm just
going to change the directory into the
original folder here and again we're
going to go into the Smalley fold
against malli list the files in their CD
form and we will create our Metasploit
directory again Metasploit CD Metasploit
again here stage and we can just leave
the stage in there so what we're going
to do is we're gonna say CD root desktop
or so we're going to copy the payload
file here so copy root desktop payload
small E and we're looking for the
Metasploit comm Metasploit sorry and
this stage and we failed that smoly file
into the root desktop original and we're
looking for the small e form Metasploit
stage directory hit enter we list the
files in there so it's
a list the files in here we have the
payload file alright so now we can move
on into the Android manifest file once
more to actually explore what's going on
so we'll go to the original Android
manifest file let me just close the
previous ones here because I don't want
to get confused with the other ones that
we had for the other application and
we'll get I will get rid of this as well
because we're not working with that
activity file so androidmanifest.xml and
now you can see with a simple
application again all we're looking for
is we're looking for the action right
over here so the Android intent dot
action main and just above this you will
get the Android name right over here so
you have Chrome Google Android launcher
stub app alright so that is the activity
that we are primarily looking for okay
so we need to look for that activity and
the directories listed right over here
so you have com Google so if your go-to
smoly comm Google Android launcher and
we're looking for the stub app alright
so again you can simply just find it
right over here stop app and we can open
that up with a text editor and we are
looking for on create sorry on create
and there we are we have the oncreate
right over here so again we're going to
create our invoke static so let me just
do that really really quickly
invoke static and are we looking for p0
curly braces always when specifying
arguments with our android sorry and
then we're looking for the ill android
and of course with the land right now
you can with with this I need to also
explain something something important if
you do want to if you have created a
payload that does use an activity this
is a great place of doing it alright I
just wanted to make sure that you guys
understood that before we continue all
right so the land ride Metasploit stage
so again let us Floyd Metasploit stage
let me just get the right yeah stage
Metasploit stage our payload and we're
looking for this particular on create
method so on on create land roid and
we're using the content and the context
here so content based on the content
and the context context is always in
capital and we'll close that up capital
V and we'll save that all right now we
can deal with the the original
androidmanifest and I'm gonna open up
the Android manifest for the payload
application because this particular
Google launcher does not have any any
useful any useful permissions so we only
have read settings and write settings so
what I'll do is we can essentially just
copy everything so we do need internet
we need the Wi-Fi state we'll just copy
everything here we'll get real get rid
of the right settings option as well and
the we can also do that right here we
don't want to muck with the original
application permission otherwise that
can affect its functionality so again
we'll get rid of right settings here
I'll get rid of right settings and now
we can save this file and hopefully we
should be able to compile this
application now without any errors as
far as I remember this was the only one
working so again before we do that let
me just try and answer some questions
harsh
de nani I love the videos I'm a commerce
students a practice that's excellent
that's primarily why these videos are
there so go ahead just enjoy practicing
that's what it's all about so again
we'll use the apk tool and we will build
so build a root desktop and we'll use
the original folder in it and hopefully
now the application there we are the
application was successfully compiled we
did get the a apt error but that was
very very a very very small error and if
we just take a look at the sorry if we
just take a look at the we just list the
files here sorry let me just list the
files you can see that under the dist
folder under the dist folder we have the
compiled application here and now that
is not signed that is something to take
into consideration but we have
successfully embedded the payload within
the Android application so now that we
have embedded it whenever we launch this
application and because it is a launcher
certainly be active and whenever the
main activity is triggered we will get
our payload session now the other videos
that I want to make is we need to
obfuscate well we need to focus on
obfuscation because that is primarily
going to be how you get the application
on a particular device and then the
other one is persistence through either
creating a script and of course that's
going to depend on on on creating a
persistent script and essentially
getting the application to run and then
finally the video i'll be making last is
how to hide the application from the
application draw alright so that's
pretty much what i'm going to be
covering for this livestream i know you
guys wanted me to cover quite a bit more
but there that's all I have time for and
I'll be making the other videos
following up so my next video on Android
will be signing the application then
making it a fully undetectable as best
as possible but for those of you who are
curious you can also use the backwash
apk the backwash script so yeah I don't
Mike telling me to change my ISP yes I
am working on that
thanks bro for this video yes this video
will be available off to the stream can
we do it to any apps above ten megabytes
yes you can do it most of the
applications but again it's all about
how the application was developed if the
application was developed differently
then in the sense that they have various
renaming for the activities for the main
activities then you pretty much will be
will have some errors we have a message
from photo /a know it on the state in
action you'll see it in action in the
next video I'll use the exact same
application and I'll show you what
happens when you try and install it
directly on the latest version of
Android which is Android 9 what will
happen on Android 9 is it'll actually
warn you that the application is
malicious and that's primarily because
we're using the reverse TCP payload if
we were using the reverse HTTP or HTTPS
and we with port 443 than that should
should potentially avoid detection but
again obvious question will be quite
important alright so I'll answer few
more questions
and in the stream here so again I really
really appreciate you guys watching the
stream are you from Kenya yes I am in
Kenya majority of the time for work
let's see how do I feel about the use of
ATP shell ADB is very very powerful I'm
guessing you're talking about forensics
right not too sure just give me a bit of
give me a bit more information no more
questions you can use the hackers ploy
tag so I can see your message a bit more
clearly yes I've heard of West parklands
I'm not sure where sparklings but I know
about parklands
let's see what's my career I mentioned
this previously I'm a network
penetration tester yeah we'll also cover
sharing methods um yeah I will do I'm
guessing you're talking about social
engineering one of my qualifications
well I'm a penetration tester so I have
Network plus Linux plus and osep those
are my professional certifications yeah
pernais colita how make it how to make
it fully undetectable yes I will be
making a video on that that is a very
again very tricky and it does involve a
bit of manual work so the scripts really
don't work nowadays
thanks bro enjoy your day I love your
channel from Ethiopia thank you very
much love to Ethiopia I appreciate your
support
the videos are gonna come daily as I
mentioned you can go over port
forwarding yes I am gonna make a video
on port forwarding manual port
forwarding they have a course on udemy
yes I have one as I said we are
migrating our courses on to the exploit
Academy which is that hack exploit dot
IO
I've been doing my CH certification what
is my best scope I am guessing your best
are opportunities that's what you mean
are there very many opportunities you
can become and you can become a
penetration tester you can work in in
forensics you can do a lot of stuff with
ch
have you tried get dry yes I did try it
I had my one of my friends our who is a
mallow analysis and reverse engineer
make the video on the channel I pretty
much I think you have checked it he's
always CP a bit hard OS CP is all about
practice as far as I know you should
pretty much just practice vuln up I'll
be also making a series on the OS CP
pressed the the prep of machines for
fall knob so I used a MUX yes I do use
the max greetings to Russia thank you
very much for joining the stream even
though it pretty much going to be ending
it in a few minutes I will be releasing
our courses on Lac exploit Academy this
weekend apologies for that let me just
re let me just open up my virtual
machine right over here
his malware analysis stuff I wouldn't
say it's stuff I think it's just really
exciting and very very different for
each piece of malware you start working
with forward most of all thank you so
much from Canada thank you glad you
enjoyed the video greetings from Poland
great love from end
thank you very much I appreciate it
you guys can post any other questions
you have left cause I'm really strapped
for time at the moment so if you have
any important questions go ahead let's
see how many years do you have I have
two years yes I have videos on OP
spoofing you can check my channel just
search for exploit ARP spoofing you
should find the video
I would do a thing of Gaudreau it's a
very good tool Gator I think it's just
very different than what anyone has ever
used before so again it's just about
it's just about getting used to it
tips on OACP learn post exploitation
learn file transfers between Linux Linux
boxes and Linux and windows boxes
learn about exploit a modification
that's very very important
binary CDF yeah a lot of CTF videos come
coming up I have a few of the CTF
challenges I'm also going to be doing
actor box live the next hosting for
Metasploit with all ports open I'm yeah
as I said I'm gonna do manual port
forwarding I'll also show you how to use
the no IP port forwarding live in Kenya
also you like you in Crete or garden not
sure what that means is it necessary to
be grad or self learned or to be a
graduate of self learned have a good
scope I think just having experience in
what and being good in what you do
really good really goes a long way you
can reach me life of akka you can reach
me via my email my email is always
linked in the community section of the
channel or hack exploit at gmail.com
that's my public Gmail Gmail address
that I use
am I an Avenger an Avenger fan no
suddenly I'm not I really haven't been
watching any of the latest movies so
apologies the v-day kolosov hi from
Italy hello you sound like Mufti mink
yes I've got a lot I actually do watch
some of these videos sometimes on
Facebook when I do get sent those videos
telling me that I do sound like him so
yeah I guess so
engi Rock yeah I've made a video on ng
rock you can check that out as well
that's very very good Eugene Lee Aussie
high from Kenya hello
did I use PowerShell no I did not his
partial I've just have a different theme
for my terminal hello from Morocco hello
any video about empire yes I'm making
videos about Android first and I'll move
on to using cobalt strike and Empire
sorry
many of you who guys want me to look at
the camera when answering the question
so I'll do that again
who writes my articles I write I write
them personally at the moment hi from
Hungary hello Bashar Assad yes that
there isn't a course yet we are
releasing this weekend as I mentioned
our first courses both version of Linux
are using a Muni amusing Linux our Kali
Linux 20 19.1 any tips to follow before
scoring well in the CH exam
I guess just read up on your notes or
read up on the handbook it should be a
multiple choice question so CH was
pretty simple for me it shouldn't be a
difficult exam at all have a good day
god bless god bless you too can you make
more videos on fail yes I will make more
videos on veil evasion I believe I have
before but I will follow them up the
problem fail is it whether you using for
example if I use an encoder with msf
venom like Shikata can I for Windows
most of the time if you're working with
Windows 10 because they have Windows
Defender constantly updated with the
latest signatures if pretty much will
not work or will be detected
my ISP doesn't support port forwarding
why is that hands asking for hosting
with all ports or particular ports do
you have access to your main router love
from South Korea same here love to South
Korea have I hacked anyone no I haven't
act anyone do bug bounty do you do but
yes I do do some bug bounty on on bug
crowd what will I do today I've already
recorded or I've already light streamed
the recording of what I wanted to do we
have a good question from James Moreno
we advice please I have a Bachelor of
Science in information systems that's a
good start a very good start and I want
to get into pen testing where should I
go from here
I would recommend taking the Network+
certification as always do if you don't
want to that's fine it just gives you
great information to begin with before
you go into anything like osep I
definitely recommend going for OS CP
security plus and pen test plus as well
which is the one of the latest
certifications CH is also very very good
if you want an introduction into
cybersecurity or I can make a detailed
video on osep tips and bug bounty videos
yes I'm gonna be showing you guys what
environment I've set up for bug bounty
videos have I got paid for any bugs yes
I've got paid for three bugs in my
lifetime I think the total to about
maybe $800 so not really any big bugs
particularly but again it's just that I
don't have the time for bug bounty work
but when I do I usually try it out
greetings to Ukraine with master got it
correct many of the issues with port
folding are because of nut-nut
configurations and if your ISP if is
particularly doing it a connected
Internet to your entire building that is
a common syndrome what's the best way to
get your payloads undetectable by
Windows Defender well I've been working
or I've been taking a look at one of
these scripts here I don't know if I can
just show you this house planning to
make a video on it it is the Phantom
evasion tool phantom evasion tool allows
you here if I can just launch it let me
let me just launch it Python phantom
evasion dot pie so let me just start
this up here phantom evasion allows you
to generate various stages here so I'll
show you this right now so you have your
C meterpreter stage I'll get to that so
you in your Windows modules you have
your shell code injection you have your
stages so if you're looking for stages
which I'm guessing you are you can find
them right over here so if you and your
64-bit stages you have your reverse TCP
virtual lock which works great if you
are looking particularly to do sort of
to essentially prevent detection by
Windows Defender
I would recommend this stage your
modules here
what is my opinion about island security
I haven't I haven't consumed any of
their courses yet but I'll definitely
try them out they look like they have
very very good courses how do you let
the terminal continue suggestions I
think you're talking about
auto-completion that is the tab based on
the current file structure or whether or
not you have the file in that particular
directory so just use your tab key and
that should autocomplete for you to the
nearest approximation yes you can and I
do recommend using reverse HTTP are on
Android because you can actually make it
you can make it sort of undetectable by
by essentially monitoring the traffic
coming from the application because
everything will be going to and from
port 443
grim hues good day from Australia same
to you sir how are you guys doing over
there how to start model analysis that's
a good question a lot of things to cover
I'll probably have to make an
introduction video to that as well cause
Rakesh Sharma asks me are the courses by
pentester academy i believe you're
talking about the sake yes there are
really good courses apologies one of my
Android devices here is giving me
notifications sorry about that
hello M Ron it's good seeing you as well
it's been a long time how you got how
you doing oh nice
sorry about that Hughes I didn't see
that 6:23 a.m. yep that that's
definitely Australia
Eric risk oh I like your recent collab
with IT career questions yes I just made
the video yesterday very very good
questions you can check that out as well
I have about one minute left to ask your
questions so go ahead and shoot you know
any rapped with eternal blue exploit I'm
not sure what you mean by that remote
access tool usually as the payload and
then which you install on the client and
then you have the server sitting on the
server really
so I'm guessing you're talking about the
exploit the actual exploit is getting
the payload installed so you can
consider the eternal blue exploit a form
of a remote access tool however remote
access tool does give you more
functionality a wife a dentist yes I
have videos on that you can check out my
the playlists I have the wpa2
penetration testing videos
life of arc I think I'm Allah sent a
notification on your form let me check I
don't think it got any other emails here
anyway that's that's that
antwuan you from India no not from India
although India is a pretty cool place
would love to visit one one one time it
looks like a really interesting place
culturally
to iron from YouTube yes the the channel
is monetized to a certain extent but
again because of the limitations in
regards to the videos that I can't
monetize I don't earn a lotta really
just goes into the hosting and stuff
like that yeah I'll definitely check on
your message out a life of a hacker
thank you very much
Krishna appreciate it
phoned bugs in which I believe I found a
bug in well there was actually a a free
bug bounty or actually God I think the
community score that was the first site
that I got a bounty on was humble bundle
which as you already know is the site
that has all of these bundles which I am
to do a giveaway on by the way I then I
believe it was a startup company that a
video a platform that I found the second
bug it was remote code execution I
believe I'll have to actually post all
of these these exact details in regards
to the bounties
this channel been on YouTube for about
three years now the the exploit
application has been inactive know cause
it was kicked off the Google Play Store
sadly because of the content that it has
Google has really release strict
Community Guidelines now I'll recommend
getting the CH first if you are
interested in it and then get the OU SCP
you have security plus that's pretty
cool
also my hacking machine setup I don't
have a dedicated setup but I do have an
environment that I do create with I do
have a collection of tools that I do use
constantly so I'll probably make a video
on that yes the video will be uploaded
when the broadcast is complete all right
I'll just be here for a few more seconds
now
yeah I think I'll pretty much end the
video here thank you very much guys for
joining me on the stream I really really
appreciate it
let me just answer one more question how
to act the same network without using
payload I'm not sure what you mean and
what devices you're talking about car
hacking videos yes I am working on a
large project on that but that is going
to involve obd the obd connection to the
vehicle because that is the most common
connector yeah so thank you so much for
watching the stream guys I really really
appreciate it
you can post any of the other questions
on my on my social networks or you can
actually contact me on my forum hag
exploit or org and yeah I'll be seeing
you guys later so thank you so much and
yeah peace